{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "认识" ,
      "answer": "Rènshì | to know (somebody)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高兴",
      "answer": "Gāoxìng | happy, pleased"
    },
    {
      "question": "可以" ,
      "answer": "Kěyǐ | may"
    },
    {
      "question": "进来",
      "answer": "Jìnlái | to come in"
    },
    {
      "question": "请",
      "answer": "Qǐng | please"
    },
    {
      "question": "朋友",
      "answer": "Péngyǒu | friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "记者",
      "answer": "Jìzhě | reporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "请问",
      "answer": "Qǐngwèn | may i ask...?"
    },
    {
      "question": "姓",
      "answer": "Xìng | surname"
    },
    {
      "question": "贵姓",
      "answer": "Guìxìng | your surname (polite form)"
    },
    {
      "question": "叫",
      "answer": "Jiào | to be called"
    },
    {
      "question": "先生",
      "answer": "Xiānshēng | Mr.; sir"
    },
    {
      "question": "语言",
      "answer": "Yǔyán | language"
    },
    {
      "question": "学院",
      "answer": "Xuéyuàn | institude, college"
    },
    {
      "question": "学",
      "answer": "Xué | to learn, to study"
    },
    {
      "question": "的",
      "answer": "De | a possessive or modifying particle"
    },
    {
      "question": "学生",
      "answer": "Xuéshēng | student"
    },
    {
      "question": "什么",
      "answer": "Shénme | what"
    },
    {
      "question": "学习",
      "answer": "Xuéxí | to learn, to study"
    },
    {
      "question": "汉语",
      "answer": "Hànyǔ | chinese (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "英国",
      "answer": "Yīngguó | Great Britain, England"
    },
    {
      "question": "加拿大",
      "answer": "Jiānádà | Canada"
    },
    {
      "question": "美国",
      "answer": "Měiguó | the United States of America"
    }
  ]
}
